klicknews.com 2016-06-09

# Privacy Policy | klicknews

  * Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

## The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on klicknews. On some pages, you can order services and make requests. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
IP Address  
(etc.)

## The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when referring our services only to sell our service and maintain the customer. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to deliver our service.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our web site if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our web site and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our web site, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

## Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. klicknews will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Klicknews stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we klicknews are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## How We Use Cookies:

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can help a web site recognize a previous visitor and remember any preferences that may have been set during earlier visits. Cookies can securely store a user's profile, personalize your use of our services and help us understand the types of resources you're interested in. klicknews use cookies on our sites to track visitor practices and determine which site features and services are most important to users. A cookie makes it possible for the user to access the site without requiring entry of a user name or password, allows the user to view different restricted areas of the site without reregistering, and allows the user to personalize the site for future use. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent acceptance of cookies.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Commission Junction, Kontera. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this webite. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to klicknews's users based on their visits to this website and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.klicknews.com send directly to your browsers. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here. These third-party ad servers automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Klicknews has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.klicknews.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

This web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and off-line.

If you have any questions about the security at our web site, you can send an email to security at contact@klicknews.com 

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our web site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our web site is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at support@klicknews.com

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
